My name is Nikita What's your name I'm from the
Меня зовут Никита Как вас Зову я из
city of Khmelnitsk call Anro
города Хмельницке звать анро Вы
Where did I understand you
откуда понял вас
Anro were talking I
анро разговаривали
remember How do you communicate
помню А чем общаетесь
Books of the film Music
книги фильма музыка
cool ro madra You know no I know why No, just
прикольно ро мадра знаете нет
a new new one I understood
пого Да нене как раз новый новый понял
you about a year ago as a
вас где-то год как выходит
regular as
регуляр как сам
the director himself  Poter from him, what am I saying? Poter from the
режиссёр Потер у него что говорю Потер у
director, realism, realism, you understand
режиссёра реализм реализм понял Вам
realistic Yes, I like the film very
реалистичный Да фильм нравится очень
realistic Yes, and I just admire it Well, how much
реалистичный Да и я просто восхищаюсь Ну
it conveys all the beauty, all let’s
насколько Он передаёт всю красоту всю
say expression, all of reality, this is
скажем экспрессию всю реальность ты вот
how you look at it You’re like How you immerse yourself, this is
как смотришь Ты как Как погружаешься вот
how it seems like it’s on Eve  was very
как вроде как оно на Еву Это было очень
talented, I understood And there are classics that you
талантли понял А есть классика вам кто
like, well, I don’t watch the classics, I understand
нравится ну классику не смотрю понял
at all, but you haven’t watched the classics and
вообще да не смотрели классику и градина
Kane’s hail Yes, you haven’t seen them, probably no no, I
Кейна Да не видели наверное нет нет
understand But well, mediocre new
понял А вот ну посредственно новые
classic films that have come out, that
фильмы классические которые вышли то
is, let’s say,
есть
since the eighties, for example,
допустим с восьмидесятого года например
since
с
the seventies, I haven’t watched  I don’t like
семидесятого не смотрю не люблю
retro, I got us anyway, what are your
ретро понял нас вобще какие у вас
favorite films, top top five of your favorite
любимые фильмы топ топ пять любимых
films Naturally jaga-jaga yes there is a
фильмов Естественно джага-джага да
series, this is the chase for the loaf
сериал есть это погоня за буханкой
the film Kill a Ninja you know these honestly there are no
фильм Убить ниндзю знаете эти честно нет
pits Well, I think so you’re probably about 4050 years old
ямы Ну я так думаю вам наверно лет 4050
42 I’m 42 and 42  I understand Well, it’s as if
42 мне 42 а 42 Поня Ну как бы просто у
we just see the style of interest also,
нас видите стилистика интерес также
for example, some people like, for example,
например кому-то нравятся например
ballroom dancing, some people like modern Well, yes, that is,
бальные танцы кому-то современные Ну да
just let’s
да то есть просто вот допустим как М
say, let’s say modern, I
сказать современные мне современные
like modern films, but still, I think that’s
фильмы нравятся но вс-таки я считаю что
also a mantra for me  classic name f I don’t
тоже манр для меня классика наме ф не
know how it is for you ma for example Then I
знаю как для вас ма например Потом
dug also from the classics such n
копала тоже из классики такой н
from Horror so modern then this is
из Хоррор такой современный то это
Evil Worms there is a
Зловещие черви есть
film Honestly I don’t know I’m only from
фильм Честно не знаю я только из
Evil
Зловещих
for now Evil
пока ка Зловещие
Dead m s interesting I think Madyar
мертвецы м с интересно Я думаю мадяр уже
may already have something similar
может что-то похожее
is filming the World Cup of the Dead, the plot is
снимает в ЧМ сюх мертвецов сюжет в том
that a group of friends came to the house and
что группа друзей приехала в дом и
it turns out that one demon moved in there,
получается одного там заселился демон
these friends moved in and one remained
этон друзей заселился и один остался
alive there, well, in short, such a chauvenous
живой там ну короче такой шовен ий
horror movie if, well, like an old guy tna
ужастик если ну как как старый пяни тна
if they looked like old Halloween like
если смотрели как старые Хэллоуин как
old nightmarish tse  Vyazov and so on, well,
старые кошмарным це Вязов и так далее ну
this very much has something in common with Madra, there’s also
это очень перекликается с мадра там тоже
like there’s also a company of friends
типа есть ещё там э рота друзей
coming and moving into a house somewhere, an
приезжает заселяется в дом где-то
abandoned house on the line of
покинутый дом на линии боевого
combat, and there, in short, something moves into them, in short, it
столкновения Да и там короче в них
starts at
что-то вселяется короче начинается вот
night like Flint, in short what  -that’s
ночью типа Огниво короче какой-то вот
how On Halloween, like there, guts
как На Хэллоуине типа там кишки
scatter then from people like someone
разлетаются потом от людей типа кто-то
Takes it away, it’s very sad Well, they
Забирает да очень печально Ну они все
were all filmed in the genre of hearing, that is,
снимались в жанре слыша то есть слыша
they heard, Everything is the same. Even if
они-то Все одинаково Вот если даже
you watch the same Nightmare of Elm Streets
посмотреть Тот же Кошмар ули вязы
Friday The Thirteenth CD one and  the same
пятницу Тринадцатая КД одна и та же то
maniac who runs after teenagers,
маньяк который бегает за подростками
who is a maniac who kills them,
который маньяк который их убивает там
the most important thing is to compete in how
самое главное соревноваться в том как
who killed whom. Well, this is a maniac running after
кто кого убил А ну это маньяк бегает за
teenagers. And here it turns out that a Magyar is
подростками А тут получается мадяр
running after
бегает за
teenagers, also such a peculiar
подростками тоже такой своеобразный
maniac Yes, I
маньяк
understand you, but is there after No, I
Да понял вас а есть после Нет я
asked  there is something to see after the
спрашивал есть после что посмотреть из
last one, the pursuit of a loaf, I understood
последнего погоня за буханкой
you, not I, from the last one in all t,
понял вас не я из последнего во во все т
I understand that you haven’t seen the pursuit of a
я так понимаю вы не видели погоня за
loaf No, it’s very interesting, well, it’s
буханкой Да нет там очень интересно ну
like an allegory, that’s what
как бы аллегория така вот Что вот у вас
comes into your head from the phrase “chase for a loaf”
возникает в голове от фразы погоня за
some kind of loaf of Mad Max, tell me what this is, this is a
какой-то Безумный Макс те с скаж вот что
chase for a loaf. What is the
что это вот погоня за буханка В чём
plot? Some kind of post-apocalypse, I
сюжет Постапокалипсис какой-нибудь там
don’t know, some bikers are chasing the main characters.
не знаю за главными героями гонятся
For example, I’m
какие-нибудь байкеры Например я же
saying something like Mad
говорю что-то типа истерики безумного
Max’s hysteria there, well almost  bikers there are
Макса там там ну почти байкеры там
flying bikers Oh well, Pony are flying but
летающие байкеры А ну Поня летающие но
they are like unmanned bikers like some
они типа беспилотные байкеры типа как
kind of feature such well there is a fantasy
типа фишка такая ну там фантастика
get Ravi science fiction with elements of
получа Рави фантастика с элементами
realism like it turns out these skies are
реализма типа получаются эти неба
like they call themselves Neo
есть они как бы они себя называют Нео
bikers they are like but not on motorcycles
байкерами они типа но не на мотоциклах
they seem to be on  aircraft, but
они как бы на летательных аппаратах но
on remote-controlled
на дистанционно управляемых летательных
aircraft, they fly in flocks, in short, they
аппаратах они вот стаями короче есть
fly Yes, they catch up with
летают Да догоняют
some bad characters Yes, and they kill,
некоторых плохих персонажей Да и убивают
like these Neo bikers flying I understand, I
типа вот эти Нео байкеры летающие понял
understand Well, you probably like this kind of science fiction
понял Ну вам наверно такое из фантастика
with realism, but I
с реализмом нравится да своим подходом
haven’t heard of my approach, and I haven’t heard of a
не слышал да
kani lover, and so
кани и так
further soon I
далее скоре м
like
нрави
m fmo a huge amount I can see a
м фмо огромное количество я видно
certain segment you are watching another
определённый сегмент смотрю вы другой
segment and somewhere our many
сегмент и где-то у нас наше множество
watched films do not intersect so much, I
просмотренных фильмов не так сильно
understand, but I from let’s say from
пересекаются понял но я из допустим из
the last one I watched all the hard I don’t know
последнего смотрел воо все тяжки не знаю
Well, it seems Cool What’s the plot  What is the
Ну вроде Прикольно А в чём сюжет В чём
plot? The plot is that
сюжет сюжет в том что
two people decided to cook and
два человека решили варить э наркотики
sell drugs. Well, if I
их продавать Ну если коротко очень
understand very briefly, one is a chemistry teacher and
коротко понял один это учитель химии а
the second is his former student. I understood
второй - это его бывший студент понял
it. It was very similar to the madra,
это е очень коротко у мадра было похоже
but it’s like there. Teach them they were good.
но там как бы Учите они хорошие были они
they cooked some kind of explosives Yes, they
варили взрывчатые вещества какие-то Да
made these some kind of capsules, filled them with
делали эти какие-то капсулы набивали
these explosives and with
этими взрывчатыми веществами и вот с
these You know, you say so, I just
этими Знаете вы так рассказываете я прям
decided to see what kind of madyar it was
решил посмотреть что это за
Look Robert Madyar jaga jaga or
Посмотрите Роберт мадяр джага джага или
Robert Madyar
Роберт мадяр
badabum I discovered this genre a year
бадабум Я открыл для себя этот жанр год
ago  I was even addicted
назад У меня вот было зависимость даже
to him, I was before bedtime, I couldn’t
от него я была перед сном я не мог
fall asleep so as not to watch the next
заснуть чтобы не посмотреть очередную
episode, I realized Robert Brody is he he he he yes
серию понял Роберт Броуди это он он он
Brody his pseudonym is
он да Броуди у него псевдоним
sthenic madyar Robert Madyar so he is
стенический мадяр Роберт мадяр так он
miles
мили
Brody
Броуди
Which episode did you
Какую серию вы там
choose there Well
выбрали Ну
now
сейчас
Wikipedia  Just get Wikipedia on YouTube
Википедию Википедию в юбе сразу
or go to Google Robert Madyar jaga jaga or
или в Гугле Роберт мадяр джага джага или
Robert Madyar badabum immediately give out
Роберт мадяр бадабум выдать сразу там
pirated excerpts there anyway
пиратские отрывки есть по-любому
Well,
Ну
perhaps a
возможно
comedy jaga-jaga Robert
комедия джага-джага Роберт
Madyar is a cool film for 50
мадяр классный такой фильм на 50
seconds,
секунд что
yes for 50 seconds No, what can you see there?  50
Да на 50 секунд Не а что там видно на 50
seconds explosion And this is clearly a pirated
секунд взрыв А это видно пиратская
cut because they steal it in Utah, these are
вырезка потому что в Юту воруют его вот
not allowed If they do it for more than 5 minutes Yes
эти нельзя Если делают больше 5 минут Да
YouTube Can ban this from this
YouTube Может забанить это из этого
film It’s protected by copyright Yes they
фильма Он же авторскими правами защищён
take rifling
Да берут
What
нарезов Что
exactly Maybe I remember this episode describe
именно Может я эту серию помню опишите
what explodes there not  I know There's a man standing here,
что там взрывается не знаю Здесь человек
bearded, bearded, he's probably like,
бородатый бородатый это он наверное типа
he's despicable as a director, that's how
он как режиссёр презен вот бородка как у
long his goatee is, yes, yes, his
него длинная
beard is long How it explodes
да да бородка длинная Как взрывается
that I don't know it's IT Let's see what's
что не знаю это ИТ Давайте посмотрим что
exploding
взрывается
Let's
Давайте
dial Robert Madyar badabum here
наберите Роберт мадяр бадабум вот
he finds him these
находит его эти
films jagu
фильмы джагу
jagu that's there Jau  there are
джагу вот там Джау там есть как
just these ones that came to the house
раз эти что приехали в дом
Viu go there is a video it’s
виу идут есть видосик этоже
just
просто
that Well, that is, if it’s like a film,
который Ну то есть если это как фильм
then it seems to me that all these songs are
снят то мне кажется вот эти все песни
copyrighted, they are protected
авторскими правами они защищены потому
because it’s just a custom that everyone films, well,
что просто обыч который снимают все ну
like in TikTok, too, Tom himself EU  I
как в тиктоке тоже Том сам ЕС Я то
looked at the horse
посмотрел коне
on
по
I told you I scored looked at what you see there is
Я же говорю забил посмотрел что там вы
an excerpt Well, I’ll say Apocalypse today
отрывок Ну так скажу Апокалипсис сегодня
looked
смотрели
no no Look, that is, there are similar
нет нет Посмотрите то есть там похожие
yes yes similar I understood
да да похожие понял А как называется
What’s the name Maybe some wrong excerpt on What’s the
Может какой-то не тот отрывок по Как
name like wat I’m now  I’ll find the vbe, it’s
называется как у ват я сечас найду вбе
also called zavo because you
тоже называется заво то что вы
watched the excerpt Madyar
посмотрели отрывка мадяр
badabum Madyar badabum I just
бадабум мадяр бадабум прямо так и
call it that How many views does this role have Yes yes yes
называю Сколько просмотров у этого роли
now I’ll tell you no there are roles that
да сейчас вам скажу не вот есть роли что
4 million 3.9 million
4 млн 3,9 млн
views jaga-jaga badabum
просмотров джага-джага бадабум
madyar just just closed the tab  I’ll
мадяр просто просто вкладку закрыл я
just write to you
сейчас прям напишу вам
like
типа
[music]
[музыка]
title
название
everything
всё
switched something immersed this
переключился что-то погруз нел этот
cinematographer
кинематографист
[laughter]
[смех]
[ __ ], I really didn’t even laugh, didn’t laugh Tod I
Бля я реально не змиг не заржать Тод я
Koli VN started shukati
Коли ВН почав шукати
there The trick is that Ponya ko you introduce
там Фишка в том что Поня ко вводишь
Robert madr jaga jaga  Yes, there is a
Роберт мадр джага джага Да выдается
video of my roulette od Yes, there are ods too, but having
видео мое рулетки од Да там тки од тоже
already understood in
нно побачив уже понял
short, the prono
короче проно
govo
гово
Apocalypse letter to my Telegram right
Апокалипсис пись на мий Telegram прям
now axis VN
зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube taking
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the srg ORV in your ban and I
нас через срг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
don’t show too much video to people every hour  do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams to that for that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
purpose for the Mali operational connection
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
to be written directly at the same time and Popik there in telegra okrim
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
video sche tezh Tsikava and
телегра окрим видео ще теж цикава и
Korisna information and we are guilty of you trimati
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
postiyny operational connection is
постийний оперативный звязок
not independent in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
write
пиши